Set up your personal and corporate
email quickly and efficiently
on your Samsung Galaxy Tab 4
10.1 from Verizon Wireless.
Watch this video to learn how.
Begin by tapping email.
Add your personal email account
by choosing an account to set up
from the list of email providers.
Enter your email
address and password.
Tap Next.
When setup has finished,
select account options like how often
your email is synced to your tablet
and tap Next.
You have the option to give this
account a name on your tablet.
Enter one if you choose.
Finally, enter your name to
show on outgoing messages.
You’re done setting up
your personal email.
Tap Next to return
to the setup page.
If you have a Microsoft Exchange account
from your work or school, tap Corporate.
Enter your Email
address and Password.
Then be sure to tap the
Manual setup icon.
Enter your domain and
Exchange Server names.
Contact your organization if you
do not know this information.
Tap Next when complete.
Read the prompt and
tap OK if you agree.
An additional prompt may
require remote security.
Tap OK to continue.
Once on the Account
options page,
change your email settings
like sync options.
When finished tap Next.
Some accounts must be
able to remotely control
some security features
on your tablet.
In order to allow a device
administrator, tap Activate.
Finally, you have the option to name
the new account on your tablet.
Tap Next to complete setup.
Tap Done with accounts to
go to your email inbox.
To view all your accounts
together, tap the account name.
Then, select Combined view.
You’re now done setting
up your email.
Enjoy the convenience of
having email on the go!