When you're on the move and you
need to manage your wireless
services, My Verizon
is the answer.
Download the My
Verizon mobile app
for your smartphone or tablet
at home, at work and on the go.
The My Verizon mobile app puts
your family's wireless account
in your hands.
Use it to view your current
summary of minutes, messages
and data usage for each
line on your account.
You can even securely
pay your bill any time
or set up Auto Pay
right from your device.
Need to add more data
to your current plan?
My Verizon is the answer.
Simply launch the My
Verizon mobile app,
and add changes to
your plan instantly.
If you have a ton of apps,
music and pictures on your phone
and need to back them up, like,
now, My Verizon is the answer.
Add features like Verizon cloud
storage directly from the app.
Even suspending a
line is no problem.
And when you're ready
to reconnect the device,
My Verizon is the answer.
View your current account
information on the My Verizon
mobile app, and update
your personal data,
like your billing
address and password.
When you need to manage your
wireless account and service,
now My Verizon is the answer.
Download it to your
smartphone or tablet today.