The Samsung Galaxy Tab
4 10.1 from Verizon
has the KitKat Android
operating system.
Watch this video to learn how
to get around your tablet.
To unlock your tablet, swipe in
any direction on the screen.
This is your Home screen.
Return to this screen at any time
by pressing the Home button.
The white indicators
at the bottom
tell you which Home screen
you are currently viewing.
Home screens are where you can put apps
and shortcuts that you use often.
Swipe to the right to see
additional Home screens.
Swipe back to the left.
Tap the Recent apps button
to open a list of recently used
apps for quick multitasking.
Simply tap on an app to open it.
Let’s go back to
the Home screen.
Touch the top of the screen
and slide your finger down to
open the Notification Panel.
This panel shows you notifications
from apps, emails, and more.
To clear a single notification,
swipe left or right.
Or to clear all
notifications, tap the X.
Open the notification
panel again.
Quickly turn on or off features
like Bluetooth and Sound
from the Settings shortcuts
at the top of the panel.
To jump to more settings, tap the Settings
icon near the top right of the screen.
Here you can change all
your tablet’s settings.
Press the Home button to
return to the Home screen.
To explore your apps, tap Apps.
Apps are programs that you
can run on your tablet.
Tap Widgets at the top of the
screen to see your widgets.
Widgets are apps that update
right on your Home screen.
In the upper right corner you have quick
access to apps you’ve downloaded.
Tap Back and select Apps to
return to the Apps screen.
Now tap the More options icon
to see additional options.
From here you can Edit
the order of your apps,
uninstall downloaded apps, change
how the apps are sorted and more.
Tap Back.
Swipe to the left/right in your
Apps list and tap Play Store.
In the Google Play Store you can
download new apps, movies, and more.
Spend time exploring your new tablet
and in no time, you’ll be an expert!