Watch this video to learn how
to set up Wi-Fi and Bluetooth
on your Samsung Galaxy
Tab 4 10.1 from Verizon.
Open the Notification Panel by touching and
sliding down from the top of the screen.
Tap the Settings icon.
Then, tap Wi-Fi.
Make sure Wi-Fi is turned on by sliding
the Wi-Fi switch to the right.
Wi-Fi will turn on and a list of
nearby Wi-Fi networks will appear.
Tap the one you
want to connect to.
If you’re connecting to a secure network,
you’ll need to enter its password.
Once done, tap Connect.
You should now see Connected
underneath the network name.
Now let’s look at connecting a
Bluetooth device to your tablet.
To set up Bluetooth,
tap Bluetooth.
Make sure Bluetooth is turned on by sliding
the Bluetooth switch to the right.
Tap Scan to get an updated list
of nearby Bluetooth devices.
Please note that the device you are attempting
to pair with must be in discovery mode
or the scan will not find it.
Once you have found the device you
want to pair with, select it.
You may need to confirm an already
existing password for pairing.
If this is the case, tap OK.
On the tablet, connected devices will
appear in the paired devices list.
Press the Home button
when complete.
To quickly turn
Bluetooth on or off,
you can use the
Notification Panel
by touching and sliding your finger
down from the top of the screen.
Then, tap the Bluetooth icon.