Wi-Fi Enhanced Connectivity makes
it easy to switch to Wi-Fi
when you’re using
a lot of data.
Watch this video to learn
about this feature
on your Samsung Galaxy
Tab 4 10.1 from Verizon.
Your tablet has Wi-Fi Enhanced
Connectivity automatically turned on.
To see how it works, let’s open
the Play Store as an example.
From your Home screen,
tap the Apps icon at the
bottom right of your screen.
Then, scroll to and
tap Play Store.
You are instantly notified that you
can connect to a Wi-Fi network.
Select the network you
want to connect to,
or tap Not now if you wish to continue
to use your mobile data connection.
If you want to turn
this feature off,
open the Notification Panel
by touching and sliding down
from the top of the screen.
Tap the Settings icon.
Tap Wi-Fi to see
your Wi-Fi settings.
Then tap Show Wi-Fi
pop-up to turn it off.
You won’t be reminded
about switching to Wi-Fi
when opening apps that
might use a lot of data.
Press the Home button
to leave Settings.
Another feature of Wi-Fi
Enhanced connectivity
is that when a Wi-Fi network you’ve
connected to before is in range,
you’ll be automatically
connected.